

# **DANIEL TERAN**

WEB/SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | PHOENIX, AZ DANIEL-TERAN.COM | GITHUB.COM/EARTHMAN12

#### **PROFILE**

Hard-working, self-motivated, and open-minded individual with experience in a variety of trades. Outfitted with a diverse background obtained from attending university for an extended period as well as a working for a NASA related research group for over five years. Excellent people skills with a desire to continue learning.

#### SKILLS

- -Languages: Python, C/C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- -Back-end Frameworks: Diango
- -Front-end Frameworks: React, Angular JS, Bootstrap

Developed apps and web pages that implement RESTful API's and SOL databases. Proficient with MS Office. Github and CAD. Up to date with technology.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **RESEARCH TECHNICIAN • UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA: LUNAR &** PLANETARY LAB • AUGUST 2016 - PRESENT

Wrote scripts and GUIs in Python using a multitude of libraries for our scientific research. Designed various parts as well as space flight hardware using Solidworks. Aligned and tested optical setups in and out of our sounding rocket. Maintained our team's weekly schedule online.

## STUDENT EMPLOYEE • UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA: FUEL MODERN **EATERY • FEBRUARY 2015 - NOVEMBER 2016**

Rotated between shifts working as a cashier, line cook, and smoothie maker. Assisted in opening and closing the restaurant which consisted of prepping food, cleaning the kitchen/dining floor, restocking, and counting the drawer.

#### **EDUCATION**

## BACHELOR OF GENERAL STUDIES IN SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY, **HEALTH & SOCIETY • AUGUST 2012 - MAY 2018 • UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA**

Studied Math, Computer Science, Physics/Astrophysics, Materials Engineering, Sociology and Astronomy





